<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sweady</title>
    <link>https://sweady.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sweady</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-fr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sweady.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://sweady.xyz/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sweady.xyz/index/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful documentation Material is a theme for Hugo, a fast and flexible static site generator. It is built using Google&amp;rsquo;s material design guidelines, fully responsive, optimized for touch and pointer devices as well as all sorts of screen sizes.
Material is very lightweight – it is built from scratch using Javascript and CSS that weighs less than 30kb (minified, gzipped and excluding Google Fonts and Analytics). Yet, it is highly customizable and degrades gracefully in older browsers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>https://sweady.xyz/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sweady.xyz/getting-started/</guid>
      <description> Installation macOS brew install sweady  Linux wget xxx &amp;amp;&amp;amp; chmod +x  Setup You must move to the folder where you want to manage the Sweady configuration.
sweady init  Configuration The previous step generates a sweady_config.json file that will contain all of the information needed to build your Sweady cluster.
Once you have finished the configuration, you must run this command:
sweady create  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://sweady.xyz/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sweady.xyz/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>Quo vadis? The port of the original Material theme has replicated nearly all of its features. A few are still missing but I&amp;rsquo;ve good news: the Hugo community is actively working on this issues. Maybe with the next release of Hugo we can abandon this list. Stay tuned.
Localization Currently, it is possible to collect all strings in a single place for easy customization. However, this only enables you to define all strings in a single language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://sweady.xyz/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sweady.xyz/license/</guid>
      <description>The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright &amp;copy; 2016 Go Container, https://gocontainer.fr
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>